Hi!
Not a bad little snazzy stroller here.
Ideal for your quick trips.
This particular stroller will accommodate a new born.
Will sit up as they get older by adjusting this rip cord back here.
You have a little inside pouch for your kid for a bottle, for some snacks.
You have your bar in the front, which is removable, a cup holder for mom or dad.
Everywhere that you say that something is labeled red means that there is a function on this particular stroller.
This is about 15 pounds in weight for this particular umbrella stroller.
Folds simple.
Pick up there, push down on the red to the right, push it forward, locks.
Easy to open.
Pull out on your lever.
Just kind of let it go down in the front, push down on the red in the back and you're ready to go.
Decent little basket.
Offers a little rain shield as an accessory.
This stroller retails for like a 129 dollars.
Great little buy.
Excellent for say the grandparents house.
Don't want to spend a lot of money but want a good quality stroller.
Something that goes from newborn on through.
Graco Mosaic is the way to go.